http://www.golite.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy StatementGoLite Brands, LLC GoLite respects your right to privacy and is committed to protecting it. The information collected about you is used to help improve our products and services. Your information will not be given to any other companies without your express consent. Because we feel your privacy is so important, we are providing this page to describe when and how we collect and use such information.
Collection of Personal Information
If you submit a product testimonial or a product suggestion, we will ask for your name, location and email address; however, you may choose not to have your name, location or email address displayed with your testimonial or suggestion.
If you request any information from GoLite, we may request your name, address and email address to provide you with the information requested.
Anonymous Information Collection
GoLite collects general usage information about visitors coming to our Web site. Some of that information may be collected with the help of “cookies” or other tracking technologies. (A cookie is a small file that a Web site writes to your hard drive when you visit that site. Cookies cannot read information from your hard drive or read information from other cookies. Cookies and other general usage information include no personally identifying information.)
Cookies and other general usage information will only be used by us internally to help us improve our Web site and your Web experience.
If you turn cookies off in your Web browser, you will still be able to access and browse most of the www.golite.com Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options and services that involve our interaction with you.
How We Protect the Security of the Personal Information You Send UsWe intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect from unauthorized access or disclosure the personal information that you share with us.
Sharing Information with Other PartiesGoLite will not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with or to parties outside of GoLite without your consent.
Policy Changes and UpdatesFrom time to time, we may use personal information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy Statement. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
How to Contact UsQuestions or concerns about this Privacy Policy Statement, or about any other matter concerning our privacy practices or the privacy of the information that you provide us, may be sent to:
Web PrivacyGoLite Brands, LLC3201 1st Ave. SouthSuite 211Seattle, WA 98134
Search
What are you looking for?
